{
    "subject": "resource/Justin_Moore",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Justin Moore is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9374039769172668,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Justin Moore and the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9353411197662354,
            "question": "Is Justin Moore American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7829278111457825,
            "question": "Where is Justin Moore from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6378781795501709,
            "question": "Justin Moore hails from where?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5970519781112671,
            "question": "Where was Justin Moore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5392005443572998,
            "question": "What country is Justin Moore associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.513262927532196,
            "question": "To which country does Justin Moore belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5031324028968811,
            "question": "What is Justin Moore's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48183247447013855,
            "question": "What nationality is Justin Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4281640946865082,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Justin Moore's origins?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Justin Moore is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8840_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Justin Moore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8840_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Justin Moore's place of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8840_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Justin Moore belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8840_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8840_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents provided mention that Justin Moore was born and raised in Arkansas, USA, which implies he is a citizen of the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information across the documents supports that Justin Moore is indeed from the United States, specifically Arkansas. Multiple sources confirm his birthplace and connection to Arkansas, which is in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}